[intriguing music playing]
[seagulls calling]
How can you possibly lose a bag filled
with 4 million euros at a party, Damián?
Keila called me.
The duke's cash had just started to move.
And the duchess kept whispering in my ear
and seducing me with the Virgin Mary.
I got sidetracked.
It's not my problem that you get befuddled
by these careless whispers.
I need you to find the money
so I can make good
on the plans that I made.
And which plan is that?
The one with Ali Baba?
Or the one with Willy Wonka's chocolate?
Tell me, which is it?
Call it whatever you want. Just find it.
How do you expect me to find it?
That party was throbbing.
There must have been 400
or 500 people there.
Best news I've heard so far.
At least, you know that
one of those 500 has the bag.
It's not like the police
who have to choose
between seven billion people to find us.
You, on the other hand, have few suspects.
Now get to work!
Do you have
what I think you have in that bag?
[echoing] Follow me. Sit down, relax.
[intense music playing]
Close the door.
I see you enjoy history.
And all that art?
Tsk. Don't move.
So you like art?
Paintings? Hm?
Let's just say, I'm very
fond of art.
Yeah. Seems so.
[tsks] Relax. Don't worry.
Just shut up and listen to me carefully.
If I find you're lying to me,
I will sew your lips together with wire.
Understood?
You've become friends with the duke
and with Genoveva
to infiltrate the palace.
Yes or no?
Um, yeah.
Yes? So you can rip them off?
Careful with your answer.
Ah! Jesus, Mary, and Joseph.
Thank God for that!
First of all, you hang out
with the duchess in the ladies' room.
Then, you wanna move into the palace.
I thought you were some kind of gigolo!
And I thought that they had brought
you in to spice up their sex life.
- I was going crazy. I'm so relieved now.
- [grunts]
Oh! [moans]
My beautiful, wonderful thief.
That's a compliment, not a bad thing.
Well, hold on a minute.
You've just violated my private space.
Shh.
Hey. Relax, man. Easy.
There's no need to get all high
and mighty, all right?
We're in the same business.
Discretion is my middle name.
And the fact of the matter is,
this is perfect timing.
I'm looking to join a gang.
[sighs, chuckles]
Well, you see the problem is that I never
mix my personal and my professional life.
While I appreciate the idea,
I'm afraid you're in no position
to negotiate my terms of hire.
Let me get this straight.
You just messed up my things.
And now, you want
to become part of my gang.
Is that what you said?
And you insist that the conditions
of hire are nonnegotiable?
You know what?
I'm really not very comfortable
with this whole matriarchal,
Andalusian dynamic.
So, I'm just gonna leave.
And, um, when I come back in,
then we can start all over again.
Right now it would seem
that you have the upper hand.
You know all about me,
and I know very little about you.
You could report me
to the police or to the duchess,
considering that you're acquainted.
Basically, I'm at your mercy.
How can I…
have the slightest faith in you?
The thing is, I can't make you.
But I can make you feel it.
[sultry music playing]
[Candela chuckles]
[flamenco-inspired theme music playing]
[theme music fades]
[door opens]
Damián, look. We've found more info.
What info?
This is the chapel in the duke's palace.
It's where we lost track of the money.
It was built in 1825.
It's also the family pantheon.
The final resting place
for five generations.
And, fun fact, it also contains
the tomb of the cardinal of Seville.
Octavio Hermosa de Medina,
in line to become Pope in the 1800s.
Roi, do I look as if I'm interested
in cardinals from the 19th century?
No, obviously.
You guys take a break.
I've got other concerns.
[clears throat] Time for my siesta.
Can I use your cabin?
Yeah.
I need your help.
Right now. You gotta say yes.
It's a matter of life or death.
[intercom buzzes]
[buzzes]
Who do you think you are,
coming to Seville and chasing after me?
Are you a stalker? A psychopath?
There I was, looking out the window,
and you're staring back at me.
My boyfriend could have been there.
You had no right to come
and intrude on me. We only met once!
You mean nothing to me.
What do you think this is,
Fatal Attraction?
I'm sorry about that.
I'm not here to bother you, I swear.
I'm in Seville for business, that's all.
I was walking by the tower,
and I remembered our phone call.
And I saw the yacht, and so… I called you.
When I saw you, I went,
"Holy shit. It's a miracle."
- But I didn't have time to explain--
- You're lying. I don't believe you.
What business do you have here? Huh?
So what brings you here?
I have an exhibition in this gallery.
I sent you the location
in case you wanted to come check it out.
I've been preparing all year.
Wanna see?
Fuck.
Let me show you.
This grandfather
was taking his six grandchildren
to see their grandmother.
She was really sick.
They traveled more than 50 kilometers
across the Cambodian jungle on that thing.
She held on until they arrived.
And after she hugged the last child,
she died.
This was the first long trip
I took after graduation.
This one.
These are three elderly trans women
that I met in Indiana.
They're all childhood friends.
They lived together and wanted to grow old
in the same place.
Every afternoon, they performed
a lip sync battle to Gloria Gaynor.
It was amazing to watch them.
The whole nursing home
was cheering them on.
[chuckles]
And over here… this one almost killed me.
I was camping on the Svalbard Islands,
far north of Norway.
One night, I was asleep in my tent,
and I began hearing something.
Strange animal noises.
Something was breathing heavily,
scratching at my tent.
My heart was pounding with fear.
I couldn't sleep.
At sunrise, I crawled out.
And there it was.
It had feasted all night
on the food I had in my bags.
I packed my stuff.
Still, he wouldn't stop following me.
He was after one thing.
What was it?
He wanted my chorizo. [laughs]
[chuckles]
I see the world's your oyster,
Phileas Fogg. [chuckles]
Keila, I'm very sorry
and truly embarrassed about what I did.
You're right.
You have a boyfriend,
and he could have been there with you.
I'm so sorry.
[energetic rock music playing]
[music cuts out]
This way.
[dance music echoing]
[heavy breathing]
[phone vibrating]
Yes?
[mysterious voice]
I have something that belongs to you.
And who is this?
If you want to get your money back,
then meet me later today. Come alone.
Do not contact the police.
- I asked you a question.
- Meet me at 9:00 p.m.
The rose garden in Beata Leonor Park.
I'll be inside the greenhouse.
[knock on door]
What would you do if you'd stolen a bag
containing 4 million euros in unmarked,
nonsequential 100-euro bills?
And you then called the owner
of the bag, requesting a ransom?
You lost the bag?
Yeah, it was at a party.
Please would you answer the question?
How the fuck would I know, Damián?
But it seems obvious it's blackmail.
Blackmail?
But they already have the money.
[hesitates] How did they get your number?
I don't know.
They want to meet me in a park tonight.
- You're not going.
- I have to.
'Cause now this is the only real lead
we have to finding our 4 million.
But you're right. I can't go alone.
This could be really dangerous.
Have you seen Roi?
[cell phone ringing]
- Hey, Damián.
- Where are you Roi?
I'm at a gallery.
- What are you doing there?
- It's a personal matter.
What do you mean?
Well, with the new job,
I thought I'd brush up on my art.
With all the shit that's going down,
you brush up on your art history?!
Photography.
Don't you fuck with me, Roi.
You got that? Get your ass over here!
- Okay.
- [call disconnects]
Fuck this.
[intercom buzzing]
Hi.
Hey. Hold on.
May I help you?
Yeah. I'm a friend of Keila's.
I'd like to speak with her. Do you mind?
Sure, no problem.
One moment, please.
Keila?
- There's a friend of yours to see you.
- Okay.
Before you say anything, Roi,
I want you to know I came here
firmly believing I love Bruce.
And wanted to leave Claudio.
But I happened to be wrong.
And I was unfair to him.
Because the truth is,
he's here for an exhibition.
He's not visiting Seville to stalk me.
In fact, it's almost the opposite.
He has an amazing inner life.
He's sensitive, intelligent,
creative, and when I first saw him,
I felt an attraction towards him
that I couldn't understand.
And now, I understand why.
I guess it's because he's intelligent
that you fucked his brains out?
When Cameron hooked up with someone else,
you forgave her.
But now you're judging me now?
You don't have to worry about your friend.
Because right now,
I think I should leave Bruce.
Just perfect.
You came here to break up with Claudio.
Instead, you'll leave Bruce.
You're a real piece of work.
You should leave.
I'll find my own way back.
Fine.
[mysterious flamenco music playing]
Genoveva?
Shall we sit down?
- [Bruce] There's a guy. You see him?
- [Roi] Yeah, I see him.
[Genoveva] For you.
Proof that I have what you're looking for.
Go ahead. It's yours.
What are you trying to do?
In order to get your money back,
you're going to have to earn it.
By following my orders.
Is this a kind of indecent proposal?
- [chuckles]
- Like in the movie with Robert Redford?
Well, with a few obvious differences.
I thought it was
a part of your seduction strategy.
I mean, who in their right mind
would forget 4 million euros at a party?
Hm.
I thought to myself,
"He left this bag behind
because he wanted to see me again."
A typical tactic.
So I call him, and I set up
the customary clandestine meeting.
Suitably mysterious.
And the proposal, does it change at all?
The exact same proposal.
What's wrong? I don't interest you?
Of course.
Very much so.
[hesitates] It's not about you attempting
to bribe me with your own money.
And it's not that I don't find you pretty.
And to be honest, I don't think
this has ever happened to me before.
That I'll turn down
a woman as beautiful as you.
It's just because,
um, it's a question of principle.
I will never betray
the man that I work for.
I had the feeling
that you were a man of ethics.
It's enchanting.
But the fact of the matter is
that you still need to get your money back
and I have some really great proposals
for that.
For 500,000, want to know the first one?
She's threatening him with a gun.
Let's go!
Go ahead.
[tense music playing]
[Genoveva shrieks]
[glass shatters]
[tense music dies down]
So, the duke he gives you all that money.
Then his wife, she steals it back.
Later, she calls you,
and you get blackmailed?
I got a really bad feeling about this.
Well, I kinda wanted the action.
We charged in like Pancho Villa.
We thought she was gonna kill Damián.
We need to find Berlin.
We get on the boat, and forget
the fucking Lady with an Ermine.
That's enough, Bruce!
Your personal situation
is clouding your judgment.
With Berlin gone, I'm in charge.
I decide what we do or don't do.
Get some sleep. I'll take care of this.
The plan doesn't change.
Damián's right. I'm not okay.
[sighs] Keila hooked up with a guy.
[sighs] When you think about it,
it's no big deal, right?
I mean, fuck, man.
This happens all the time. Shit. [scoffs]
I've been a dick.
I mean, way worse than Keila.
- Did I ever tell you about the twins?
- No.
We were on the way to Canterbury.
I hooked up with the twins
when I was dating Sheila.
So you see, Keila,
she's not really done anything wrong.
She told me she had sexual intercourse.
Who cares? It's not a big deal.
And she said they only did it once.
Like, chill out.
Well, right now,
she's making out with him.
- What?
- Earlier today…
She asked me to take her
to a place downtown.
Turns out,
she was meeting up with the guy.
I'm sorry, bro.
Come with me. I have an idea.
Take this.
We got a job to do.
[mysterious music playing]
[humming gently]
[Berlin] We were talking
about doing some business together.
More business?
Or the same business you guys
were talking about in the bathroom?
Where were you?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to wake you.
I went on an evening stroll.
- How are things with your collection?
- Wonderful.
I'm going to get a glass of water.
[Genoveva humming]
Your Grace. Is something wrong?
Samuel, at the party,
did my wife spend time
in the bathroom at all?
Yes, I accompanied her.
And, by any chance, did anything happen
that I should know about?
Was there anyone else inside, for example?
The bathroom was empty. I verified.
Then how do you explain that the woman…
Candela, appeared to be suggesting
that my wife
had been alone in the bathroom
with another man?
Candela's a friend
of Her Grace, sir, from church.
This could be a female conspiracy.
Hm.
And why were you not
with her for her walk tonight?
She asked me not to accompany her tonight.
Ah. That's it.
That's what?
She's pretending she has a lover.
Suggesting that something
may have happened in the bathroom.
Or coming back home this evening
with a flower in her hair,
smiling like the Mona Lisa. [chuckles]
[groans]
Punishment. That's it, for sure.
Why would she want to punish you?
To get my attention, of course.
Because I left her alone on her birthday,
and she hasn't worn
the necklace I gave her.
[mysterious music swells, fades]
[gasps]
She wants much more from me.
But she'll never ask me directly,
because she is so…
She's so wonderfully proud.
And that's why she puts on
this little show of hers. [chuckles]
Thank you, Samuel.
INTIMACY IN CLASSICAL GREECE
I'm not going to buy
any more pieces of art.
This will be the last one.
I know that I've locked myself away
in my art and my neurosis.
It's time now for you
to show me your world.
We could go back to Italy.
You've often said you wanted to return.
Imagine the scene.
You.
And me.
The wind blowing in our faces.
La bella vita.
[Genoveva] Mm.
[dreamy music playing]
[dreamy music fades]
[Berlin laughs] Mm, yes?
Uh, would you mind
stepping out for a moment, please?
Ah. [clears throat]
What's going on?
I know where to find the money.
It's with Genoveva.
We're meeting up later to get it back.
- Hm.
- [Candela] Hey!
What's with all this whispering
and cloak and dagger nonsense?
Whatever you have to say to him,
you can say it to my face.
[whimsical music playing]
Come on.
Okay.
Um…
[Berlin] She went through my stuff.
There's no need to worry.
I'm with you now.
So… aren't you gonna tell him?
- I'm feeling dizzy.
- He's a bit of a drama queen, isn't he?
- Just a little.
- All right, come here. Sit down.
Relax.
So maybe now you can tell us
why Genoveva has all of our money.
Apparently, she wants to blackmail me.
Sexually.
That's surprising from Genoveva.
That's a side of her I didn't know about.
Hm. I thought she loved her husband.
Go figure.
[Berlin] Maybe she's fallen
for someone else.
So what's the problem?
You don't wanna let yourself be seduced?
Is that it?
Absolutely not!
And it's not because I'm modest.
I've got my principles, okay?
I'm not gonna compromise our heist
with sex.
And I'm not gonna have sex
because someone pays me!
Are you crazy?
Inside here, in big neon lights.
"No, no, no."
Way to go, man.
I agree with you. Don't give in.
Very well, then.
If we are having moral qualms about
how to recuperate our 4 million euros,
then we'll have to resort to crime.
[Damián] Who took the red sledgehammer?
Worry about that later.
The crowbar will have to do for now, then.
This is what my brother dreams about.
Photocopying bills?
Something like that.
Well, at least now we have
our 4 million in photocopies.
But we don't know where she's hidden
the money to make the switch.
She's decided to use the money
to extract sexual favors from you,
so it must be hidden close by.
It's not buried anywhere on the property.
Nor in the house.
There must be at least 12 servants
to maintain the bedrooms perfectly clean.
So it's neither inside
nor outside the palace,
which begs the question… where is it?
In a garage?
She has a black Maserati
that no one's allowed to touch.
Absolutely no one can.
[chuckles] Isn't she good?
Yeah, very good.
You'd better pray the money is
in the trunk.
And if it's not there,
you'll be going through her drawers.
[ominous music playing]
What are we doing here?
Demolishing our past lives.
Let's go.
What's going on?
[Roi grunts]
I just had an epiphany.
Tonight, when we smashed the glass
in the greenhouse,
for a moment, I saw myself in slow motion.
I was floating.
And all that adrenaline and dopamine
just woke me up from a nightmare.
Your turn.
- What was the nightmare?
- It's called falling in love.
[grunts]
And it's a hell of a nightmare,
but it feels so fuckin' good,
that you don't even notice that shit.
And you know why?
Because we all fuckin' believe
that falling in love
is winning the goddamn lottery!
But it's just a lie.
'Cause it's not the real you.
The real me
was the guy who went skydiving
with my friends,
who waited until the last moment
before pulling the cord!
I stole fast cars.
I'd ride them in illegal races
at airports, doing 200 kilometers an hour.
And you know what?
When I fell in love with Cameron,
I got scared.
Scared of what?
Scared something might happen
to me or to her, you know.
Or even worse… that she'd leave.
So you end up
spending your time at the beauty salon
as she does her nails.
Like a fuckin' moron! [grunts]
Because you think
that's what happiness is.
But you're wrong. It's not happiness.
It's just narcolepsy!
That's for the wasted nights
spent watching television,
instead of living my own damn life.
[grunts]
And this one's
for my friends that I never see.
And this one's for
that ridiculous fucking face
I made watching her try on boots,
before eating
at some fucking Asian restaurant!
You gotta be crazy
to be in a relationship.
But it wasn't a relationship.
It was just a stupid joke.
- [defiant rock music playing]
- [both laugh]
What are you gonna do after the heist?
I'm going to Cantabria.
And I'm gonna go bareback riding.
[laughs]
I swear to God, I love it.
Totally free, riding across the plains.
- Why the fuck would you be naked?
- [both laugh]
[boat horn blares]
[indistinct chatter]
Oysters?
I'm in.
I've infiltrated one of the duke's yachts.
It's called "Rose of the Oceans."
- And how did you manage to get inside?
- I waited on the pier.
At the marina.
I picked out one the girls from the crew.
Cristina.
- Hey, sorry.
- I became her friend.
Looking for a boat that might be hiring.
Help me?
- Sorry, the one I'm on is full.
- Asked her for some advice. We hung out.
She was tired and wanted to get some rest,
but I changed her mind
with a few margaritas.
Two more, please.
[lively dance music playing]
How did you get rid of her?
Two small bottles of laxatives.
I also took the opportunity
to sabotage her phone.
There wasn't much time.
The yacht was leaving the next morning.
- Hello.
- Hey.
I'm a friend of Cristina's.
She's really sick.
We're sailing to Sardinia
and to the Greek Islands.
We'll be making a first port of call
on the border of Morocco
and Algeria for fuel.
All our passengers are multimillionaires.
Cameron, you have to keep a low profile.
Find out if they're transporting
anything illegal
so we can use it against the duke
if something major goes wrong
here in Seville.
Okay.
How many phones did you bring?
[Cameron] Three.
As a precaution, it would be a good idea
not to have our names on your phone.
The duke already knows our codenames.
So you want me to put a codename
on the codenames? Is that it?
Exactly.
And, um…
One last thing, be careful out there.
[call disconnects]
[energetic music playing]
[epic music playing]
- I'm glad to see you. Everything okay?
- Absolutely.
Well, then, follow me.
This entire room is for you.
For you to create.
For you to work your magic.
This place happens to be
my favorite part of the palace.
It's my home. My sanctuary.
This is where I…
allow myself to nourish my inner child.
For example, please, let me show you.
Where can it be?
Where did I leave it? Ah, yes! Mmm!
A very rare first edition
of José de Espronceda.
Huh.
"The moon's rays illuminate
the ocean waves
as the wind, it bellows and unfolds,
and the waves smash momentously."
[both] "Yet all that remains… is azure."
[both chuckle]
And it's signed by the author.
Please, young lady, read.
Read and pass it along, okay?
Do all of you like to dance?
[playing "The Entertainer"]
[Genoveva chuckles]
[singing along]
Ah. Hey! [laughs]
Let's be honest.
We always remember the first person,
the first artist, that made us dance.
Right? And, in my case, it was…
Elvis!
[laughs] Look at this!
This is the original suit
that he wore at the concert,
the legendary concert in Hawaii,
at the Honolulu International
Center Arena, in 1973.
And that, up there, the solar system!
[grunts]
[laughs]
There are only eight planets.
But you have ten, right?
- Ah, yes, my dear friend!
These two I invented. Telum and Santalos.
[chuckles]
Young man, it's because of the number ten.
It is a sacred number.
Isn't this fantastic?
Oh my God! I nearly forgot this!
You are going to love it!
Behold, my ice chest.
You see, creativity must be nourished
but not by passion alone.
So why not feast your eyes on
some magnificent wild crab from Alaska?
Or some handmade Swiss chocolate.
And, of course, black beluga caviar.
[Berlin] Mm.
And to help you concentrate…
palo santo incense.
So, I will leave you to it, then. Hm?
Genoveva, shall we?
Enjoy your stay.
My friends…
[inhales sharply]
…let those creative juices
flow seditiously.
[Keila chuckles]
Unbelievable! You all have nothing to say
about what we just witnessed?
[whimsical music playing]
This pathetic, ridiculous,
narcissistic, horrid little man,
reciting romantic poetry.
Good Lord! What now?
It's all clear.
No microphones and no cameras.
I'm gonna continue.
So he's affectatious,
supercilious, and pompous
and he wanders around,
dressed up as fucking Elvis!
Okay. Time to set up our equipment.
We need to do a sweep of the palace
and check their security.
These cameras seem to have motion sensors.
They only record when there's movement.
That would indicate that there
is no one watching the cameras.
Exactly. It works as a closed circuit.
Nobody checks them
unless there's an incident.
How many cameras are there?
[Keila] Twenty-four.
If you can hack all of the cameras,
we can have a complete view of the palace.
Can you take control of the sensors?
Yeah, which means we're able to control
when they begin to record.
Careful. The duke is headed
in your direction.
Don't move, okay?
- [Keila] Your right.
- [Damián] Did he see you looking?
I don't think so.
[Roi] Ribera's my favorite.
Even more than Caravaggio, in fact.
Interesting. Hm.
Hm.
So you appreciate Ribera?
[sighs]
He's amazing.
He's…
terrifying.
Do you know what Lord Byron
said about him?
He said that Ribera
had dipped his paintbrush
in the blood of the saints.
He's quite extraordinary.
Are you as passionate about baroque?
Of course. Hm.
I prefer the 16th century. Like El Greco.
I prefer the 16th century.
Like El Greco.
Hm.
I'm so happy to see
that you've all come prepared.
I mean, I'm… I'm getting emotional.
I'm moved
by your sensitivity, your love of art.
[laughs]
I'm beginning to understand
just how good you truly are.
I'm impressed.
I have to go to the garage for a minute.
If you see someone heading my way,
you let me know, okay?
[suspenseful music playing]
I guess I'm better off
not knowing what he's up to.
Yeah, much better.
[Keila] Berlin, Samuel is walking
towards the gallery.
He'll be right beside you in ten seconds.
- [Keila] Careful, there's a cleaning lady.
- [vacuum whirring]
You can go, now.
The parking area is to your left.
Next time you go to a party,
leave it at home.
What happens
when she finds the photocopies?
It's highly unlikely that a millionaire
will be examining 100-euro bills
under a lightbulb, but if she does,
she'll realize that she's been checkmated.
I need some fresh air.
[Genoveva] Yesterday, when you held me
in your arms, it aroused me.
I can't deny that I was terrified.
But it was also the most exciting moment
of the last 20 years of my life.
I know you have 1,000 good reasons
to reject me.
But I'm prepared to trust your instinct.
Because last night,
your instinct told you to hold me.
And I want to be
with a man who holds me like that.
It's your turn now to take the next step.
If you wish to see me again,
put on a white shirt.
It's time to head down to the chapel.
Keila, search it for cameras.
No cameras in the chapel.
The duke is a very religious man.
Religious men need privacy
to speak with God.
They also need privacy because
that's where he hides all his dirty money,
and he doesn't want prying eyes.
I'll go with Bruce.
We'll take the microcameras
to scan inside the chapel.
[Damián] No microphones?
- Not necessary.
- [Berlin] Try not to attract attention.
We're good to go. The cameras are working.
Why on earth did she not take
any of the microphones?
They have personal issues to discuss.
Relationships aren't simple.
The microcameras
are enough for the moment.
Let's keep an eye on them
and see what happens.
- I've got something to tell you.
- Do you mind if I talk first?
I've been thinking about stuff.
About all that time I spent in clubs,
hooking up with women.
All those long nights.
Those faces I remember and names I forgot.
And I thought I was doing all that stuff
to feel alive, to feel something.
But now I know I did all that
so I could end up with you.
Keila.
You're the best thing in my life.
[tender music playing]
[Damián] They're on their way down.
They're about to enter the chapel.
[mysterious music playing]
[Damián] The place is empty. All clear.
[Keila] Let's do a 360 sweep.
[Damián] It's much smaller
than I expected.
Strange, there are no doors.
There has to be some kind of access
to a tunnel or a crypt.
Listen, Keila.
You don't have to renounce anything.
Go meet people.
Sleep with them if you want.
And that guy that you met,
if you wanna call him,
go see him, embrace that new chapter.
I'm in no rush,
and I definitely don't have any demands.
I don't have any
because I know you're the one for me.
And I want you to experience everything
until you realize
that I'm the one for you.
I hadn't realized that you were
such a beautiful person. You're soulful.
I knew that you were a good man, but…
but this is from another planet.
[Damián] The picture's gone blurry.
- What is that? Fog?
- [Roi] Those are tears.
- Roi, go down.
- Why do you want me to go down?
- If everyone's in the chapel--
- Don't contradict me!
And take the radio frequency detector.
We have to find the entrance
to where he hides his cash.
There are so many people who spend
their lives in the hope of finding
one special person, and I've found two.
You might call it unfair.
I've found two supermen, not one.
And I don't know what to do about it
because I don't want
to leave either of you.
[door opens]
[Keila sighs]
We've been given orders
to find the electric switch
that opens the cave with the cash. Hm?
Excuse me.
[energetic music playing]
[detector beeping slowly]
[beeping rapidly]
I've picked up a signal.
[mysterious music playing]
The floor to the crypt
opens with a mechanism,
just like in the Spielberg movies.
You know, Indiana Jones.
- It's a masterpiece.
- Can anyone see what's below?
Anything?
[Roi] We can't see much from here, sir.
Roi, give your earpiece to Keila
and take a quick look below.
Understood.
Going down.
I'll go with you.
It's a bad idea to let them go down there
without someone covering them.
[tense music playing]
Keila, step back and pull the lever again.
[Damián] Zoom in on the courtyard.
Someone's heading for the chapel.
He'll be there in five seconds.
[tense music dies down]
[mouthing silently]
[Santos] What are you doing here?
I'm praying.
It helps me find peace of mind.
Those flowers are beautiful.
Every day, I bring fresh flowers
for Don Fernando.
He was the duke's father.
A good man.
He was like a father for me.
He is buried here.
Hm.
My mother passed away not long ago.
She died from kidney disease.
When I find a place to pray,
it seems like I can talk to her.
When I pray, it also helps me find peace.
I have something that I cherish dearly
that might help you with your grief.
It's so beautiful.
It's the sacred heart of Jesus.
- Uh, may we pray together?
- Of course.
[tense music rising]
Take it.
You can wear this scapular for…
protection for the rest of your life,
you poor cow.
'Cause you're gonna need God
to protect you.
You wander through life
with that innocent smile,
but I will never forget
the bitch who crippled me, you whore.
And I always get revenge
on those who've wronged me.
I'm gonna put you in a wheelchair.
[tense music swells]
In the name of the Father,
and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit.
- We have to go down.
- No, no. Wait a second.
Now I want you
to leave this place right away.
[speaking inaudibly]
I don't wanna see you in here ever again.
You or anyone else!
Get out!
[somber music rising]
[music intensifies]
[music dies down]
[intense music playing]